<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Fitness Blog!</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 13:25:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bodybuilding Basics Nutrition</title>
		<link>/2021/07/17/bodybuilding-basics-nutrition/</link>
					<comments>/2021/07/17/bodybuilding-basics-nutrition/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gitesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 13:25:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Nutrition]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=8</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Good nutrition, like good training, is simple &#8211; learn the basics and practice them consistently. We have on our hands a zillion ways to diet, feed ourselves and live our lives for fitness. Let&#8217;s clear the air and put some things in order. Good nutrition, like good training, is simple—learn the basics and practice them [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Good nutrition, like good training, is simple &#8211; learn the basics and practice them consistently. We have on our hands a zillion ways to diet, feed ourselves and live our lives for fitness. Let&#8217;s clear the air and put some things in order.</p>



<p>Good nutrition, like good training, is simple—learn the basics and practice them consistently. A little knowledge and a lot more discipline is the secret. Apply yourself diligently—look ahead, don&#8217;t look back and don&#8217;t look for shortcuts. There simply aren&#8217;t any.</p>



<p>Health and fitness has climbed to the top of America&#8217;s popularity list and has become big business. As you&#8217;ve noticed, there&#8217;s a gym on every corner and a glut of diet and bodybuilding formulas to pack on muscle and burn off fat. Competition is fierce, the promises are bizarre and we&#8217;re all confused, suspicious and eventually numb. We have on our hands a zillion ways to diet, feed ourselves and live our lives for fitness. Let&#8217;s clear the air and put some things in order.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2021/07/17/bodybuilding-basics-nutrition/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5 best exercises for bigger biceps</title>
		<link>/2021/07/17/5-best-exercises-for-bigger-biceps/</link>
					<comments>/2021/07/17/5-best-exercises-for-bigger-biceps/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gitesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 13:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Exercise]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=5</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[1. Dumbbell Concentration Curls Sit on a flat bench or chair with your legs open and forming a “V” shape. Now, hold the dumbbell in one hand and slightly lean forward. Place the elbow of the arm holding the dumbbell on one thigh and rest your other hand on the other thigh. Curl the dumbbell slowly towards [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>1. Dumbbell Concentration Curls</strong></p>



<p>Sit on a flat bench or chair with your legs open and forming a “V” shape. Now, hold the dumbbell in one hand and slightly lean forward. Place the elbow of the arm holding the <a href="https://www.gqindia.com/look-good/content/the-only-13-dumbbell-exercises-youll-ever-need">dumbbell</a> on one thigh and rest your other hand on the other thigh. Curl the dumbbell slowly towards your shoulder while twisting your wrist slightly so that the palm faces your shoulder. Then slowly bring it back to the starting position. Do this for 15 reps for each arm. </p>



<p><strong>2. One-Arm Dumbbell Preacher Curl </strong></p>



<p>This is one of the best exercises to increase the overall size of your biceps. For this, you can either use a preacher bench or the back of your sofa (basically any surface that provides a downward incline). Hold the dumbbell in one hand using a strong underhand grip. Keep your elbows fixed to the surface and slowly curl the dumbbell up and then bring it back to the starting position. Do this for 15 reps for each arm. </p>



<p><strong>3. One-Arm Tricep Extension </strong></p>



<p>You can do this exercise either standing or in a seated position. Stand straight with your feet slightly less than shoulder-width apart. Hold a dumbbell in one hand and take it behind your head with your elbow bent and pointing towards the ceiling. Now, slowly extend your arm upwards and then lower it and bring it back to the starting position. Repeat this for 10-15 reps for each arm.  </p>



<p><strong>4. Incline Push-Ups </strong></p>



<p>An elevated version of the traditional push-ups, you can try this exercise using a bed, couch or a sturdy chair or a box that won’t move while performing it. Stand in front of the bed or a chair and place your hands on the surface. It should be shoulder-width apart. Now take the plank position and ensure that your body forms a straight line and your lower back isn’t drooping. Once you take the position, bend your arms to lower your chest towards the bed or the chair and push your body back up to the starting position. Do 10 reps x 3 sets for starters. </p>



<p><strong>5. Hammer Curls</strong> </p>



<p>To begin this exercise, stand with your knees slightly bent and feet shoulder-width apart. Hold the dumbbells in your hands (you can either do this exercise holding the dumbbells in both hands or one at a time) with palms facing each other. Keep your elbows fixed at the side of your body and only move your palms. Curl the dumbbells up and then slowly lower it down and return to the starting position. Do 15 reps x 3 sets for each arm to really work on the brachialis, which plays a great role in building the biceps. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2021/07/17/5-best-exercises-for-bigger-biceps/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>/2021/07/17/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>/2021/07/17/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Gitesh]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 13:15:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http:/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2021/07/17/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
